Menu Open Full Site Navigation

Close Overlay  

### Live coverage of starting

00:

### : LIVE NOW

Privacy Policy
==============

Last modified: January 14, 2015

**A. Introduction**

By your use of the Website, you consent to be governed by this Privacy Policy.  
  
**B. Definition of Personal Information**  
  
Personal Information may include your name, email address, age, gender, country, postal code, IP address, nickname, image, and biographical information (“Personal Information”).  

**C. Children’s Privacy**

This Website is for adults and is not directed to children under the age of thirteen (13).  You must be at least 13 years of age to use this Website.  By accessing and using the Website, you represent and warrant that you are at least 13 years of age and have the right, authority, and capacity to enter into this Agreement and to abide by all of the terms and conditions of the Agreement.  If you use this Website outside of the United States, you are responsible for complying with the laws and regulations of the country from which you access, download, or use the Application.    
  
Haymon does not knowingly collect and/or share Personal Information about children under the age of thirteen (13) on the Website.  If, in the future, Haymon collects Personal Information from children, it will do so in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act.    
  
**D. Personal Information and Data Security**  
  
You can visit and browse the Website without disclosing any information about yourself.  However, to participate in any Services (i.e., to submit postings in connection with various features of the Website, including blog posts, and articles, and to register to receive newsletters and fight alerts), you must register and provide accurate information about yourself to the Website.    
  
This Website contains links to websites that are not operated by Haymon.  These third parties may collect data from you and share some of that data with us or others.  Haymon is careful when choosing its partners, sponsors, and affiliates, but Haymon is not responsible for any misuse of personal information by such third parties.  We recommend that you view the privacy policy posted on each website that you use to confirm that the site’s policies are acceptable to you.   
  
Any Personal Information you provide to the Website is protected from unauthorized disclosure by commercially reasonable technological measures.  While Haymon strives to protect your personal information by encryption and other means, Haymon cannot guarantee or warrant the security of the information you transmit to us, and if you choose to use the Website, Services, and/or Content, you do so at your own risk.  There may be additional security risks if you provide your Personal Information over a public or third-party network.  Please keep in mind that the information disclosed by you on the Website—for example, information you may provide to others in responding to blog posts, articles, and the like that may be available on the Website—may be collected and used by visitors to the Website. 

WHILE HAYMON TAKES COMMERCIALLY REASONABLE PRECAUTIONS TO SAFEGUARD YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, HAYMON DOES NOT GUARANTEE COMPLETE SECURITY.  
  
Personal Information may be used for marketing and promotional communications by Haymon.  Haymon will, not, however, sell or lease your personal information to third-parties not associated with Haymon.  Haymon respects the right of each user to decide whether to receive such information.  If you do not wish to receive marketing and promotional communications from us or our partners, sponsors, and affiliates, you can choose to opt-out when providing your Personal Information to Haymon.      

The Website or Haymon may be sold, or other transactions may occur in which Personal Information is one of the business assets transferred by Haymon.  In such a case, your Personal Information may be one of the assets we transfer.  If this occurs, you will be notified if there are any material changes to the way your information is collected or used.  
  
**E. Aggregated Information**  
  
To evaluate the Website and ensure that we are providing Content and Services of interest to you, we may collect and store statistical information regarding how you use the Website, the name of your Internet Service Provider, the website that referred you to the Website, and the time and date you view the Website.  We may also use Personal Information to develop demographic information regarding Website users.  Such aggregated information will not identify you personally.  We may share this aggregated, statistical information with our partners, sponsors, affiliates, and other third-parties. 

**F. Cookies, Anonymous Identifiers, and Local Shared Objects**  
  
From time to time, Haymon may place a cookie, anonymous identifier, or Local Shared Object (“LSO”) on your computer.  A “cookie” is a small line of code that is stored in your browser when you visit a cookie-enabled website.  An anonymous identifier is a random string of characters used for the same purposes as a cookie on platforms, including certain mobile devices, where cookie technology is not available.  An LSO is a collection of data stored as a file on a user's computer.  Cookies and LSOs allow us to track and keep records on user activity.  Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies and LSOs.  If you set your browser to reject cookies or LSOs, it is possible that some parts of the Website will not function.  Moreover, to use the Services, your browser may need to accept cookies and/or LSOs.  

**G. Log Files**  
  
The Website automatically collects information pertaining to your access of the Website.  Such information may include your Internet protocol (“IP”) address as well as other connection and usage data or information. 

**H. Device Information**

We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information).  A unique device identifier is a string of characters incorporated into a device by its manufacturer and can be used to uniquely identify that device.  Different device identifiers vary in how permanent they are, whether they can be reset by users, and how they can be accessed.  A given device may have several different unique device identifiers.  Unique device identifiers can be used for various purposes, including security and fraud detection, syncing services, remembering a user’s preference, and providing relevant advertising.      
  
**I. Disclosure for Law Enforcement Purposes**

Haymon reserves the right to access and disclose Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests, to operate its systems properly, or to protect itself or others.  Haymon may attempt to obtain the prior consent of the individual before disclosing the Personal Information, but it has no obligation to do so. 

**J. Residents of the European Union**

If you are an individual resident in a Member State of the European Union, you acknowledge and agree that Haymon may collect, use, and disclose your personal data as described in this Agreement, or any amendments hereto.  You further acknowledge and agree that we may transfer and process your personal data in the United States and/or outside of the European Union.  If you do not consent, please do not use the Website.   
  
**K. Unsubscribe/Opt-out**  
  
Upon your written request, Haymon will remove your personal information from Haymon’s database (which will end your use of the Website’s Services).

**L. Updating Your Personal Information or Deleting Your Account**  
  
You may change or update your personal information or delete your account by clicking on the Unsubscribe link contained in emails from Premier Boxing Champions.     
  
**M. Notification of Changes**  
  
Haymon reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time.  Please review the Agreement from time to time to ensure your familiarity with its terms.  Your continued use of [www.premierboxingchampions.com](http://www.premierboxingchampions.com/) following changes to the terms constitutes your acceptance of our amended terms.  

Follow Us:

© 2024 by Premier Boxing Champions

Close Overlay  

* Get Fight Alerts
* Follow Us:

Close Overlay
